=Manbo Destiny=
=مصير مانبو=
=Episode 12=
=الحلقة 12=
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Hey.
يا.
Weren't you injured?
ألم تُصب بأذى؟
You haven't broken a limb.
لم تُصب بكسر في أحد أطرافك.
Not your concern.
ليس من شأنك.
Mengmeng, are you okay?
منغمينغ، هل أنتِ بخير؟
Wen Shanna.
وين شانا.
What were you doing just now?
ماذا كنت تفعل الآن؟
Why do you care what I'm doing?
لماذا تهتم بما أفعله؟
Guan Mengmeng.
قوان منجمينج.
If you curse me again,
إذا لعنتني مرة أخرى،
I swear,
أقسم،
next time,
المرة التالية،
something will definitely happen to you.
سيحدث لك شيء ما بالتأكيد.
Come on, I'm not afraid!
هيا، أنا لست خائفاً!
Wen Shanna!
وين شانا!
Let go of me.
اتركني وشأني.
Let go of me!
اتركني!
Mengmeng. (Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org)
مينغمينغ. (تابعوا فريق الدعم على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org)
Lin Ge, keep your Princess under control.
لين جي، حافظ على سيطرتك على أميرتك.
Keep yours under control.
حافظ على سيطرتك على نفسك.
Mengmeng.
منغمنغ.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
Liar. Get lost.
كاذب. ارحل.
Mengmeng.
منغمنغ.
These two
هذان الاثنان
are unbelievable.
لا يُصدق.
Did you
هل أنت
get hurt?
هل تعرضت للأذى؟
Move away!
ابتعدوا!
I really didn't mean to lie to you.
لم أقصد الكذب عليك حقاً.
If you can forgive me,
إذا استطعت أن تسامحني،
I…
أنا…
I'll do anything.
سأفعل أي شيء.
Really?
حقًا؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Anything?
أي شئ؟
(You got a deal, Song Pai.)
(تم الاتفاق يا سونغ باي.)
Hi everyone!
مرحباً جميعاً!
I'm your palace girl, Xiaodoli Mengmeng.
أنا خادمتك في القصر، شياودولي مينغمينغ.
Welcome to my livestream.
أهلاً بكم في بثي المباشر.
We've got a very special guest today.
لدينا ضيف مميز للغاية اليوم.
Let's give him a warm welcome.
فلنرحب به ترحيباً حاراً.
He might be a little shy,
قد يكون خجولاً بعض الشيء،
so give us a second.
انتظرنا لحظة.
This guest right here
هذا الضيف هنا
is the dream guy of nine hundred million girls in Manbo Kingdom.
هو فتى أحلام تسعمائة مليون فتاة في مملكة مانبو.
Our First Prince of Manbo Kingdom, Prince Song Pai.
أميرنا الأول لمملكة مانبو، الأمير سونغ باي.
Let's welcome him!
فلنرحب به!
Say hi.
قل مرحباً.
Say hi?
هل تريد أن تقول مرحباً؟
Do you still want me to forgive you?
هل ما زلت تريدني أن أسامحك؟
Hi everyone, I'm Song Pai.
مرحباً بالجميع، أنا سونغ باي.
(First Prince is so handsome.)
(الأمير الأول وسيم للغاية.)
(The host is so pretty.)
(المضيفة جميلة جداً.)
Looks like Prince Song Pai is still insanely popular.
يبدو أن الأمير سونغ باي لا يزال يتمتع بشعبية هائلة.
Alright, no more talking,
حسناً، كفى كلاماً.
let's introduce our first product.
لنقدم لكم منتجنا الأول.
It's the scent
إنها الرائحة
of the prince.
الأمير.
"Let's have the First Prince try it."
"دعونا نجعل الأمير الأول يجربها."
Okay, babes, no problem.
حسناً يا عزيزتي، لا مشكلة.
Let's try it.
لنجرب ذلك.
- Try it? - Try it.
- جربها؟ - جربها.
(I really like this host.)
(أنا معجب حقاً بهذا المضيف.)
(Love it.)
(أحبها.)
(Drop the link!)
(أرسل الرابط!)
Describe how it smells.
صف رائحته.
No problem, babes.
لا مشكلة يا حبيبتي.
(This pairing is so good.)
(هذا الثنائي رائع للغاية.)
(They're totally flirting.)
(إنهم يتغازلون تماماً.)
(I really like the First Prince.)
(أنا معجب حقاً بالأمير الأول.)
It has this
يحتوي على هذا
light, subtle wine note,
نكهة نبيذ خفيفة ورقيقة،
and a warm, woody scent that feels really comforting.
ورائحة خشبية دافئة تبعث على الراحة حقاً.
It smells amazing, babes.
رائحتها رائعة يا حبيبتي.
Oh?
أوه؟
Your babes are saying
حبيباتك يقولون
they want to smell the First Princess's scent too.
إنهم يريدون أن يشموا رائحة الأميرة الأولى أيضاً.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
(This is so ship-worthy.)
(هذا يستحق النشر على متن السفينة.)
(Kiss, kiss!)
(قبلة، قبلة!)
(We can't wait anymore!)
(لم نعد نستطيع الانتظار أكثر من ذلك!)
(First Prince, you got this. Kiss her!)
(أيها الأمير الأول، أنت قادر على ذلك. قبّلها!)
(Hurry up and kiss!)
(أسرعوا وقبّلوا بعضكم!)
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
We're live.
نحن نبث على الهواء مباشرة.
They're asking for a kiss.
إنهم يطلبون قبلة.
(Kiss, kiss!)
(قبلة، قبلة!)
(Hurry up!)
(أسرعوا!)
It's selling like crazy.
إنها تُباع بشكل جنوني.
As expected of Song Pai. You nailed it.
كما هو متوقع من سونغ باي. لقد أبدعت.
(Song Pai...)
(سونغ باي...)
(He really is charming.)
(إنه حقاً ساحر.)
(I almost lost it just now.)
(كادت أن تفلت مني الآن.)
(Wait, did I already lose it?)
(لحظة، هل فقدت صوابي بالفعل؟)
(But I'm just a contracted princess.)
(لكنني مجرد أميرة متعاقدة.)
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
These past few days,
خلال الأيام القليلة الماضية،
although the royal family
على الرغم من أن العائلة المالكة
has done everything to raise funds,
لقد بذل كل ما في وسعه لجمع التبرعات،
the situation
الوضع
in the southern disaster zone is simply too severe.
الوضع في منطقة الكوارث الجنوبية شديد للغاية.
The money we've raised
الأموال التي جمعناها
is nowhere near enough.
هذا غير كافٍ على الإطلاق.
Recently,
حديثاً،
the southern areas
المناطق الجنوبية
have faced serious shortages
وقد واجهوا نقصاً حاداً
of supplies and funds.
من الإمدادات والأموال.
The two princes'
الأميران
fundraising deadline is almost here.
اقترب موعد انتهاء جمع التبرعات.
How are your preparations coming along?
كيف تسير استعداداتك؟
Father,
أب،
Mengmeng and I have
أنا ومنغمينغ لدينا
raised funds through cross-border e-commerce
تم جمع الأموال من خلال التجارة الإلكترونية عبر الحدود
and foreign trade partnerships.
والشراكات التجارية الخارجية.
We've raised two hundred million.
لقد جمعنا مئتي مليون.
This amount can already be put into disaster reconstruction.
يمكن بالفعل تخصيص هذا المبلغ لإعادة إعمار المناطق المتضررة من الكوارث.
Two hundred million?
مئتا مليون؟
That's impressive.
هذا مثير للإعجاب.
It really is.
هذا صحيح بالفعل.
Only two hundred million.
مئتا مليون فقط.
Hmph.
همم.
Father,
أب،
Wen Shanna and I have also raised tens of millions
لقد جمعنا أنا وشانا أيضاً عشرات الملايين
through real-sector investments.
من خلال استثمارات القطاع الحقيقي.
And moving forward,
وبالمضي قدماً،
there'll be even more funds coming in.
ستتوفر المزيد من الأموال.
Good.
جيد.
Very good.
جيد جدًا.
- Thank you, Father.
- شكراً لك يا أبي.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك،
the First Prince being able to raise funds so quickly
قدرة الأمير الأول على جمع الأموال بهذه السرعة
is certainly something to celebrate.
هذا بالتأكيد شيء يستحق الاحتفال.
However, in my view,
لكن في رأيي،
the First Prince and the First Princess
الأمير الأول والأميرة الأولى
appearing so frequently in public livestreams
يظهر بشكل متكرر في البث المباشر العام
is really
هو حقًا
beneath the dignity of the royal family.
دون مستوى كرامة العائلة المالكة.
Right?
يمين؟
(That old fox.)
(ذلك الثعلب العجوز.)
(Making trouble when the country's in crisis.)
(إثارة المشاكل في وقت الأزمات التي تمر بها البلاد.)
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك،
I've also paid some attention to the Firstn Prince's
لقد أوليتُ بعض الاهتمام أيضاً للأمير الأول
and First Princess's livestreams.
وبث مباشر للأميرة الأولى.
I actually find them quite refreshing.
أجدها في الواقع منعشة للغاية.
These are screenshots I saved on my phone.
هذه لقطات شاشة قمت بحفظها على هاتفي.
Take a look.
ألقِ نظرة.
Aren't they rather interesting?
أليست مثيرة للاهتمام؟
Oh my.
يا إلهي.
This is...
هذا هو...
This is outrageous!
هذا أمرٌ شائن!
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك،
we didn't steal, and we didn't rob anyone.
لم نسرق، ولم ننهب أحداً.
We even managed to raise money for disaster relief.
بل إننا تمكنا من جمع الأموال للإغاثة في حالات الكوارث.
So how is that improper?
فكيف يكون ذلك غير لائق؟
That said,
مع ذلك،
since Mr. Saul believes
لأن السيد سول يعتقد
that livestreaming with the First Prince damages the royal image,
أن البث المباشر مع الأمير الأول يضر بالصورة الملكية،
why not
ولم لا؟
have Mr. Saul try livestreaming himself?
هل يمكن للسيد سول أن يجرب البث المباشر بنفسه؟
Why you little...
يا لك من...
You're pretty witty.
أنت ذكي جداً.
Then let's do it
فلنفعل ذلك إذاً
the way the First Princess suggested.
بالطريقة التي اقترحتها الأميرة الأولى.
Your Majesty…
جلالتكم…
I don't know how to do livestreams.
لا أعرف كيف أقوم بالبث المباشر.
Mr. Saul livestreaming?
هل يقوم السيد سول بالبث المباشر؟
Would anyone even send him gifts?
هل سيرسل له أحد هدايا؟
I'll register an account tomorrow.
سأقوم بإنشاء حساب غداً.
I'll send him gifts myself.
سأرسل له الهدايا بنفسي.
I'll even make a burner account.
سأقوم حتى بإنشاء حساب وهمي.
I really want to see what he's actually like.
أريد حقاً أن أرى كيف هو في الواقع.
What are you looking at?
ما الذي تنظر إليه؟
Your necklace.
قلادتك.
I wear it every day, don't I?
أرتديه كل يوم، أليس كذلك؟
When you wear it,
عندما ترتديه،
have you ever seen
هل سبق لك أن رأيت
anything strange?
هل هناك أي شيء غريب؟
Something strange?
شيء غريب؟
You mean
تقصد
that person from three hundred years ago who looked like me?
ذلك الشخص الذي عاش قبل ثلاثمائة عام والذي كان يشبهني؟
How much do you know about it?
ما مدى معرفتك بهذا الموضوع؟
I checked the archives.
لقد راجعت الأرشيف.
It was basically a tragic couple,
كانا في الأساس زوجين مأساويين،
and they left behind a sad legend.
وتركوا وراءهم أسطورة حزينة.
What do you think our relationship to them is?
ما رأيك في طبيعة علاقتنا بهم؟
Come on.
تعال.
What relationship could there be?
ما هي العلاقة التي يمكن أن تكون موجودة؟
Even if I look exactly like someone from three hundred years ago,
حتى لو كنت أبدو تماماً مثل شخص من ثلاثمائة عام مضت،
I'm still me.
ما زلت أنا.
The one and only Guan Mengmeng.
غوان مينغمينغ، الفريدة من نوعها.
Why are you always so fearless?
لماذا أنت دائماً بهذه الجرأة؟
With you by my side,
وأنت بجانبي،
I always feel like
أشعر دائماً وكأنني
there's nothing we can't handle.
لا يوجد شيء لا نستطيع التعامل معه.
There's no enemy I can't defeat.
لا يوجد عدو لا أستطيع هزيمته.
You're exaggerating.
أنت تبالغ.
My Princess is the best in the world.
أميرتي هي الأفضل في العالم.
(Song Pai, at least you've got good taste.)
(سونغ باي، على الأقل لديك ذوق جيد.)
Fundraising can't wait.
لا يمكن تأجيل جمع التبرعات.
I'll go pick products first.
سأذهب لاختيار المنتجات أولاً.
(Guan Mengmeng, oh Guan Mengmeng…)
(جوان مينجمينج، أوه جوان مينجمينج…)
(He's a real prince.)
(إنه أمير حقيقي.)
(You're just a small e-commerce seller.)
(أنت مجرد بائع صغير في مجال التجارة الإلكترونية.)
(Don't get ideas.)
(لا تفكر في الأمر.)
(Get a grip.)
(تمالك نفسك.)
Curse that Guan Mengmeng.
تباً لذلك غوان مينغمينغ.
Making me do a livestream
أجبروني على القيام ببث مباشر
just to embarrass myself.
فقط لأحرج نفسي.
I don't even know how to do this.
لا أعرف حتى كيف أفعل هذا.
What am I even selling?
ما الذي أبيعه أصلاً؟
Huh?
هاه؟
Coffee?
قهوة؟
What is this?
ما هذا؟
That's perfume.
هذا عطر.
Can this even sell?
هل يمكن بيع هذا المنتج أصلاً؟
Um…
واحد…
We're starting now.
سنبدأ الآن.
Babes.
يا حبيباتي.
I've already negotiated the price down for you.
لقد تفاوضت بالفعل على تخفيض السعر من أجلك.
Three…
ثلاثة…
Two…
اثنين…
One…
واحد…
Go!
يذهب!
What nonsense is this?
ما هذا الهراء؟
Go where?
إلى أين نذهب؟
What go?
ماذا يحدث؟
(Host, can you try it?)
(يا مضيف، هل يمكنك تجربتها؟)
(Can you describe how it smells?)
(هل يمكنك وصف رائحته؟)
(Does this coffee taste good?)
(هل طعم هذه القهوة جيد؟)
If it's good or not, just buy it and find out.
سواء كان جيداً أم لا، اشتره واكتشف بنفسك.
There are a few flavours anyway.
هناك بعض النكهات على أي حال.
Buy it and drink it, then you'll know.
اشتره واشربه، عندها ستعرف.
Obvious, isn't it?
واضح، أليس كذلك؟
(Why aren't you smiling?)
(لماذا لا تبتسم؟)
What's there to smile about?
ما الذي يدعو للابتسام؟
I feel like crying already.
أشعر برغبة في البكاء الآن.
And you want me to smile?
وتريدني أن أبتسم؟
(Is he always this fierce?)
(هل هو دائماً بهذه الشراسة؟)
(The host is so cold.)
(المضيف بارد جداً.)
(Bro, you're way too scary.)
(يا أخي، أنت مخيف للغاية.)
(So icy I'm gonna die.)
(الجو بارد جداً لدرجة أنني سأموت.)
Die?
ال؟
Who's killing you?
من يقتلك؟
I wouldn't dare.
لن أجرؤ على ذلك.
That'd be illegal.
سيكون ذلك غير قانوني.
I'm doing a livestream here, I can't have anyone dying.
أقوم ببث مباشر هنا، لا يمكنني السماح بموت أي شخص.
No killing.
ممنوع القتل.
Just buy stuff.
اشترِ الأشياء فحسب.
No killing, okay?
ممنوع القتل، حسناً؟
(Follow the stream, everyone.)
(تابعوا التيار يا جماعة.)
(This host is hilarious.)
(هذا المذيع مضحك للغاية.)
(Hahahahaha.)
(ه ...
What is this thing doing to me?
ماذا يفعل بي هذا الشيء؟
Why do I look like this?
لماذا أبدو هكذا؟
What kind of mess is this?
ما هذه الفوضى؟
This is...
هذا هو...
This is outrageous.
هذا أمر شائن.
I'm done streaming.
لقد انتهيت من البث المباشر.
Bro, can you add more stock?
يا أخي، هل يمكنك إضافة المزيد من المخزون؟
I didn't get any.
لم أحصل على أي شيء.
(Bro, I missed it.)
(يا أخي، لقد فاتني ذلك.)
(Host, add more, I didn't get it.)
(يا مضيف، أضف المزيد، لم أفهم.)
Add more stock?
هل تريد إضافة المزيد من المخزون؟
How?
كيف؟
The stock...
السهم...
It's sold out, so add more.
لقد نفدت الكمية، لذا أضف المزيد.
Sold out already?
هل نفدت الكمية بالفعل؟
That's insane.
هذا جنون.
Oh wow.
يا للعجب!
I just said a few words and it's gone?
قلت بضع كلمات فقط، ثم اختفى كل شيء؟
Guess livestreaming really does work.
يبدو أن البث المباشر فعال بالفعل.
Alright, I'll add more.
حسنًا، سأضيف المزيد.
Adding more stock.
إضافة المزيد من المخزون.
But how do I do that?
لكن كيف أفعل ذلك؟
Adding more…
إضافة المزيد...
Where did everyone go?
أين ذهب الجميع؟
(The king praised Song Pai's emerging economic model,)
(أشاد الملك بالنموذج الاقتصادي الناشئ لسونغ باي )
(and the e-commerce boom is surging.)
(وتشهد التجارة الإلكترونية ازدهاراً كبيراً).
The news about His Majesty praising Song Pai
الأخبار التي تفيد بأن جلالته أشاد بسونغ باي
has already spread everywhere.
لقد انتشر بالفعل في كل مكان.
All the investments we talked about earlier
جميع الاستثمارات التي تحدثنا عنها سابقاً
have pulled out.
انسحبوا.
So how much did we lose?
إذن، ما مقدار الخسارة التي تكبدناها؟
We're already in debt.
نحن مدينون بالفعل.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
I'll find a way to convince other investors.
سأجد طريقة لإقناع المستثمرين الآخرين.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Don't apologise.
لا تعتذر.
You've done your best.
لقد بذلت قصارى جهدك.
If anything,
بل على العكس،
I barely did anything useful.
لم أفعل شيئاً مفيداً تقريباً.
I should be apologizing.
كان عليّ أن أعتذر.
Have some water.
اشرب بعض الماء.
(No one has ever been this good to me.)
(لم يكن أحد لطيفاً معي إلى هذا الحد من قبل.)
♪I do this for you♪
أفعل هذا من أجلك
♪The love is fake♪
♪الحب زائف♪
♪The love is true♪
♪الحب حقيقي♪
♪For you♪
♪لكِ♪